

COMPUTER ENGINEERING TECHNOLOGY

A highly-skilled computer engineer who specializes in both hardware and software engineering. This individual works with embedded systems, artificial intelligence, machine learning, and automation technologies with a strong desire to excel in their professional career and help the company meet its goals.

<u>Download Resume</u>

EXPERTISE

- HTML
- CSS
- Phyton
- C C++ C#
- Hardware

REFERENCE

Wendy Anas

Web App Programming Professor in Technological University of the Philippines

Sean Casin

Computer Science Technology Teacher in St. Anthony School, Singalong Manila

EDUCATION

2020-Present

Batchelor of Engineering Technology major in Computer **Engineering Technology**

Technological University of the Philippines

2018-2020

Science, Technology, Engineering and Mathematics

St. Anthony School

CERTIFICATION

2020

Frontend Developer

HBD Construction Firm in partnership with Topserve Sevice Solutions, Inc.

EXPERIENCE

2019 - present

Thorben Official

Computer Engineer

Supervise team testing of products in development. Observe and document performance of the system and its components. Draft and assemble user manuals for finished systems.

2019 - present

UnKnoWnCheaTs

Frontend Developer

Programming language: Java, C, C++ and HTML Operating Systems: Windows, Mac, Linux and Android, including other mobile platforms

AWARDS

2020

Developer Master

Students are given the opportunity to compete in contests involving computer programming and computer science.

2019

CS Award

The Department of Computer Science will on occasion bestow department awards upon our students who have demonstrated exceptional achievement.

INTEREST

J

Music

Books

 \mathfrak{M}

Travel

CONTACT

Metro Manila, Philippines +63 927 5410 852 lnztumala1@gmail.com

SOCIALS

{ /lance.tumala.9



X /Ransuu